[birds chirping]
[tense music playing]
[in Portuguese]
[rustling]
[footsteps on car]
[monkey shrieks]
[both breathing heavily]
Ana.
Ana!
[adventurous music playing]
[speaks Portuguese]
[shouts in Portuguese]
[shouting in Portuguese]
[muffled scream]
[person]
We start tight on a full moon.
[ominous music playing]
Milky. Almost yellow.
And we crane down
to reveal an idyllic,
suburban street.
We float past a series
of white picket fences,
until we settle
on a sewer grate.
Pow! Flies open!
Something big
and scaly slithers out,
fast, hungry,
definitely not human,
as a pulsating score kicks in.
[vocalizing]
[suspenseful music playing]
We're on the back of the beast
as it slithers menacingly
towards a little blue house.
[hissing]
[vocalizing]
[suspenseful music continues]
Wait. I'm sorry.
This is our wedding video
you're talking about?
Yes, though I actually
don't think of them as videos.
They're more like short films.
Yeah, because I'm not
sure this is quite
what we had in mind.
Okay. I know.
It's a little different
than normal, but--
We really liked the one
you did for Karen and Bart.
When they walk by the river
-and jump up
and high-five.
-That jump was dope.
And I loved
that song they used.
♪ I don't want to wait
For our lives to be over ♪
♪ I want to know right now
How does it feel ♪
[bride] You know it. Yeah.
Um, guys.
Uh, here's the thing.
I really like you guys.
And you said
you're horror fans,
and I'm like,
"I love horror so much."
And I thought this
could be special.
You know what I mean?
This is a film
you're gonna watch
for the rest of your lives.
But this isn't a film, Doug.
This is a wedding video,
and we want one
where they do a little jump.
[groom] Yeah.
[dad] Now, can you do that
for us or not?
[vocalizing]
Okay.
And do you mind
if I'm doing warm-ups?
Is it okay?
Oh, yeah.
I've seen much crazier.
Okay, good.
Does it sound better
to say my line,
"His vision is blurry,
which could suggest..."
or, "His vision is blurry,
Or I could-- You know what?
I could even do, like,
an accent. I could do just...
I think you just
should do it the way
you auditioned it, honey.
-Yeah.
It's been a while
since I booked anything,
and I just want it
to go well.
-Yeah.
-I just...
It's hard out there.
[groans] Sorry.
Doctor number 3,
we're ready for you.
[makeup artist]
Okay, knock 'em dead.
Okay, thanks.
Thank you, Donna.
Hey, by the way, if you ever
need anything from Lowe's,
I will hook you up
with my employee discount,
no questions asked.
Okay?
[chuckles] Okay.
Thanks.
Ten more ccs of tramadol.
Any idea what
I'm looking at here?
[in British accent]
He said his vision was blurry,
so, you know,
that could suggest--
Optic neuritis.
Already ruled that out.
[bell ringing]
-[director] Cut.
-[assistant director]
That's a cut!
[director] Hey, buddy,
not sure what that accent is.
Just do it normally, okay?
We're gonna go again
right away.
[assistant director] Set.
[speaking slowly]
He said his vision was blurry,
which could suggest--
[director] Cut!
Say the line faster. Okay?
Faster this time.
[rushed]
He said his vision was blurry,
which could suggest--
Cut! Jesus, I think
we gotta fire this guy.
Can we get
somebody else in here?
["Have You Ever
Seen the Rain?" playing]
♪ When it's over
So they say ♪
♪ It'll rain a sunny day ♪
♪ I know
Shining down like water ♪
♪ I wanna know
Have you ever seen the rain? ♪
Griff, it's Doug.
I just ran into your mom
at the supermarket.
She said you booked
a big gig today.
I'm proud of you, bud.
Everyone in Buffalo
misses you.
I love you. Come visit, man!
[knocks]
[gasps]
Jesus, Jerry.
Doug, what is this thing
about-- there's some kind
of a sewer monster?
Oh, boy.
[sighs] Doug.
Look, I get that this is not
what you dreamed about
when you were a kid.
But dreams, they go. Huh?
Now, I'll be retiring soon.
And, Doug, it is only
a matter of time
before all this is yours.
Really?
Yeah.
Look around. Take it all in.
And imagine.
If you do it right,
it's a pretty sweet setup
we got here.
This is a B, and maybe even
a B+ life we're talking about.
Hmm.
[spouse]
Are you sure you don't wanna
do anything
for your birthday?
You used to make me
celebrate your half-birthdays.
[Doug chuckles]
Let's go get a beer.
Or something.
[gasps]
Maybe we just watch that new
mountain climbing doc.
About the lady that
falls to her own death?
Yeah.
Fine, we can do the one
about the free diver
in the Maldives.
Who drowns?
Jesus Christ, Doug.
I don't know. Let's just take
a gummy and go to bed early.
Surprise!
[cheering]
[upbeat music playing]
Oh, my God, Malie. No!
Oh, yes. Yes, you love
a good, big birthday party.
Dad, should've seen your face.
-You knew about this?
-It was my idea.
Buddy, take my coat, please.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hey! How are you?
Yeah. Happy birthday!
Jesus, Kenny. My back!
I'm sorry.
No! That's not...
The actual lotion.
The actual basket.
"It puts the lotion
in the basket"?
eBay, buddy.
Dude, that is sick.
Yeah, no,
that is actually sick.
Oh!
Happy birthday, Dougie.
Thanks for making
the trek, Claire.
You know I love Buffalo
this time of year.
The slush, the hypothermia.
What's up? No Trent?
No Trent.
Ever again, in fact.
He started banging
his dental hygienist.
Ugh.
Anyway, tonight is all
about you, baby.
It's about me.
It's about you.
[gasps]
[laughs]
You came! Here you are.
Oh, my God.
It's been too long, pal.
It's so good to see you.
It has been way too long.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for coming out here.
Think I'm gonna
miss this? Never.
Oh.
We got a lot
of catching up to do.
Many years ago, a group
of young, passionate artists
had a vision.
It was a vision that's not
particularly original
or even, uh, good...
[guests chuckle]
...but it was theirs.
And so they made
that vision a reality.
And, without further ado,
I present to you
a completely unrestored print
of 13-year-old
Doug McCallister's
masterpiece, The Quatch.
[gasping]
What? I thought we lost
all the copies of that!
No way.
Nope.
I found it in my mom's garage.
It was stuck in the player.
Are we sure this is okay
for the kids to watch?
Who gives a shit?
Mrs. Brown had us bleep all
the swears
so we could show it
at the school assembly.
Yeah, which didn't
make much sense
because we were very clear
about it being R-rated.
-Happy birthday, pal.
-[laughs]
This isn't happening.
[Griff] Oh, it's happening.
Here we go.
[laughs]
God.
Here, sit.
Oh, I'm gonna kill you.
[gasps]
[guests laugh]
-I haven't changed a bit.
-[all laughing]
Holy ****!
Oh!
-[Claire] Look at the grass!
-Hot on the trail!
-Look out for the quatch.
-[guest] Here we go.
Before you **** strike me,
I need to **** ask you
one **** thing.
You got some **** bite left?
Or you all **** bark?
Boom!
Damn, we'd been watching
a lot of Scorsese.
We didn't quite have
the ear for it, did we?
-I need to tell you something.
-What is it?
[young Claire]
That I love you.
I've always loved you.
And I always **** will.
[young Griff]
I **** love you too.
Now, kiss me, woman.
[guests chuckle]
So much charisma.
Already, you had it.
I still can't believe
I let Doug talk me
into doing that.
What are you talking about?
That was your idea.
-[guests chuckling]
-[Doug] Yeah!
-It's coming for us.
-[young Claire] We're trapped.
[young Kenny]
What the hell are we gonna do?
-[Claire] No!
-[Doug] Yes.
Oh, my God.
We're all gonna die!
[dramatic music playing on TV]
This is where it gets real.
Not on my watch, mister.
-Boom!
-Yeah!
[guest] Amazing!
[guest] So good!
That's probably
the best birthday gift
I've ever received.
I didn't even
know it existed.
Well, I'm giving it to you.
Plus the TV
'cause you can't get it out.
Yay!
Yes!
It was right after,
you know...
Right after senior year
of college.
Yes, that's when
Anaconda came out.
Remember?
We saw it like 30 times.
Put it right there
alongside the classics.
Totally. How about that cast?
Come on.
J.Lo, Ice Cube,
Owen Wilson, Stoltz.
Oh, for sure.
I mean, it's a murderers' row.
Plus, that snake was
like a metaphor
for our lives at that moment.
Like, how life is
coming at you, you know,
hunting you
and forcing you, like,
off your...
like your parents'
health insurance and stuff.
-[Kenny] I don't know...
-[Doug] No, that's true.
-Yeah, that's...
-[Doug] It was like that.
-[Claire] That's right, Kenny.
-Whatever.
How about that accent
by Jon Voight?
How about that?
That was a choice.
[imitating Jon Voight]
"They wrap around you
until you get the privilege
of hearing
your bones break...
Bones break...
...before the power of embrace
causes your veins to explode."
Sorry.
I have the rights to Anaconda.
What?
Yeah.
Apparently, the movie was
based on a novel by some
dead Japanese guy.
And my agent introduced me
to his widow.
Unbelievably, she was such
a fan of the four episodes
that I did on S.W.A.T...
-Who isn't?
-...that she gave me
the rights.
[chuckles] Dude.
So what are you
gonna do with them?
Uh, well, not me.
Us.
We're gonna reboot the thing.
Indie-style.
Three weeks, run-and-gun
in the Amazon.
Skeletal crew.
Claire, you and I can star.
Kenny, you shoot it.
Doug, you direct.
Huh? Come on. What do you say?
I mean, it's a wonderful idea
in theory, but...
I'm in!
I can get time off from work.
Yes, you can, Kenny. Sweet!
Kenny, what are you
talking about? You're in?
He's not... No. He's not in.
He says one thing
and you're in already.
You're going to the Amazon.
He's not in.
What do you say, Claire?
I... I just...
Come on.
I don't know if I'm
in the right headspace...
Of course you are.
...with the divorce.
Of course you're not
in the right headspace.
That's the best headspace.
Are you kidding me?
Come on,
it's like Eat Pray Love
and... shit.
Come on.
You know what? I'm in.
-What? Really?
-Yes! Sweet.
Yeah. I mean, my life
is totally shit anyway so...
God, I'm so happy
to hear that.
Hmm.
I mean, not that your life
is shit, but that you're in.
Besides, as soon
as Doug says yes,
we'll probably need you
to finance this whole thing.
What?
[mouthing] Thank you.
Doug?
[gentle music playing]
Griff, I'm sorry.
I got responsibilities.
I got Malie, Charlie, my job.
I know. Making wedding videos.
Films. Right.
It's a good life, you know?
It's a B, B+ life.
B, B+ life?
It's a good life.
Do you remember
when we were kids
and we would stay up
till 4:00 in the morning,
hanging out
in your mom's basement
watching horror movies?
Scaring the shit
out of ourselves.
Texas Chainsaw
on, like, repeat.
Now we have the chance
to make one ourselves.
Dude, it's what we dreamed
about ever since
we were little kids.
I hear ya.
But we're not
kids anymore, Griff.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. I know. All right.
I just...
I get it. I do.
I get it.
Still watching The Quatch.
[chuckling]
Charlie, why don't you go
check on those cookies?
[sighs] Okay,
but I'm pausing it, so...
don't touch it.
Gonna need some ice-cold milch
with that.
[Charlie] You got it.
What are you doing?
What?
Just go make the movie.
Malie.
Come on.
Every time you watch
this thing, you light up.
Like I haven't
seen you light up
in a long time.
So what? I'm supposed to chase
some Hollywood fantasy
I had as a kid?
Waste a bunch of money
and time, and for what?
In the end,
what's it gonna change?
Okay.
[upbeat music
playing on video]
-[bride and groom chuckling]
-[bride] We hope you come
to celebrate...
[groom] As we become...
[both] The Hansons.
Holy shit.
["I Don't Want to Wait"
playing]
[sighs]
♪ I don't want to wait
For our lives to be over ♪
♪ I want to know right now ♪
-♪ What will it be? ♪
-[Doug]
♪ ...what will it be? ♪
♪ I don't want to wait
For our lives to be over ♪
What am I singing?
[knocking]
[Griff] Hey, dude.
[panting]
I don't want to wait, man.
Our lives could be,
like... over.
What...
What are you talking about?
The Anaconda thing.
You were serious, right?
Yes, very.
Then let's do it.
Let's reboot Anaconda.
["Baby Got Back" playing]
Yes! Yes.
♪ My anaconda don't ♪
All right, budget-wise,
soup to nuts,
what does it cost
to get this thing made?
I figure we need
three weeks of shooting.
Some VFX, some SFX,
a riverboat,
a riverboat captain,
travel to and from a jungle,
and a gigantic real snake,
preferably a rental.
Rental, copy.
[Doug] All in,
two, two-and-a-half
million dollars.
[whistles] That sounds right.
We've approved a loan
for you for up to...
$9,400.
Yes!
I've revised the budget
down to...
$43,000 all in.
That sounds more right.
[Doug] Now, the film
does have to be scary, right?
Terrifying. But it can't
just be about a giant snake
killing people.
Exactly.
You know?
It has to be
about something, right?
Right.
I mean...
Themes.
Come on.
Like grief.
What about revenge?
In terms of themes,
that's like one
of the top ones.
-Oh, my God. I got a good one.
-Hit me.
Intergenerational trauma.
[scoffs] I love
intergenerational trauma.
Who doesn't love
intergenerational trauma?
-It's the best.
-We're onto something here.
["Baby Got Back" ends]
[breathes deeply]
This is a masterpiece.
You're a goddamn genius.
I love it.
Don't change a word.
Not a word.
Dude, you killed it.
It's scary, emotional,
funny when it needs to be.
-Romantic.
-Dude, thank you.
Hey, Doug...
[exhales]
I know that we had
our little dustup, but...
I need to shoot
this film, man.
[Griff] Dustup?
Yeah. He fired me
from the wedding video stuff
'cause I got a little wasted.
He knocked over
the wedding cake.
-But I'm dealing with it.
-Like, getting sober?
Yes.
Well, I mean, Buffalo sober.
Buffalo sober?
Just beer and wine.
And then some
of the lighter liquors.
But definitely not all of 'em.
I'm proud of you.
Doug?
[inhales deeply]
If I'm being honest,
I enabled you a little bit.
Of course you get
a second chance.
Let's do this.
-Nice!
-Thank you, man.
[horn honking]
[Malie] Car's here.
And you have
the mefloquine, right?
You only take that
once a week.
-Hey, Dad. I almost forgot.
-Hmm?
-Talk to me.
-But I got you this.
What?
I know. Pretty sick.
"World's greatest Doug."
-I thought it
should say, "Dad."
-Whatever, man, it's funny.
-I love it. It's much better.
-[Charlie chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[monkey chattering]
[people chattering
indistinctly in Portuguese]
[sighs]
[intriguing music playing]
-[Doug] So it begins.
-Yeah!
[Doug] Oh, yeah.
All right.
[Claire] Whoo!
Made it.
-[Griff] Whoa. We're here.
-[Doug] That's what
I'm talkin' about!
Brasília!
[Kenny] Oh.
So, hey, I was reading
about anacondas on the plane.
Basically, they wait
in the water for days,
stalking their prey,
never moving, just waiting,
and then when a prey comes...
[imitates snake constricting]
...snatch and grab.
Thousand pounds of pressure.
Think you're gonna get away?
You're not.
Crushing you.
Oxygen leaving your lungs.
[imitates suffocating]
Oh, God, it's terrible.
-So, like in
the movie Anaconda.
-Yeah, exactly.
So it's real?
[passerby] Yeah,
it's all real.
Very real.
[tense music playing]
There's this story
about this woman...
God bless her.
The snake wraps
around her so tight...
the eyeballs just...
[imitates explosion]
No.
No way.
Yeah, it was
my grandmother, Sylvana.
Shit.
Horrible grandmother.
But still sad.
[Kenny] Huh.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Carlos Santiago.
Yeah, you can
call me Santiago.
-Hey! It's Kenny.
-[Santiago] Yeah, hey.
Kenny from the phone. Hey.
Kenny. Kenny, hey.
Hi.
Yeah, this is
our snake handler.
[Claire, Doug] Oh!
-[Claire] Thank God.
-He's supposed to be the best.
No. "Supposed to be"?
We have a joker here.
No. I am the best. Yes.
Oh. That's good.
[Kenny] Yeah.
So, welcome to Brazil.
Let's meet the snake.
[people chattering
indistinctly]
[tense music playing]
[in Portuguese]
[patrons speaking Portuguese]
When I found him,
he was dying of starvation.
His food supply
destroyed by gold miners
who put mercury in the river.
-[Griff] Gold miners?
-Gold mining poisons our land.
Their greed
almost killed my snake.
[Claire] Oh.
[Santiago] But I fed him,
I nursed him back to life,
and in many ways,
he did the same for me.
Ah, yes.
A tale as old as time.
Saved by a snake. [chuckles]
What's your name?
What's... Uh, Griff.
Okay, Griff.
He's not only a snake.
He's my tiny giant, my friend.
One of the most
important creatures
of the herpetological world.
No, of course... I... Sure.
I didn't... I wasn't
trying to... I... Yes.
Okay. Let me introduce you.
[trunk opens]
Heitor.
[Claire] Heitor?
Oh, my goodness.
Hey, cutie.
-Oh, no. Not cutie.
-Oh, my...
-[Doug] Oh...
-[all exclaim]
Oh, hell yes!
This thing is nuts!
There are rumors
of 'condas even bigger.
Maybe four
or five times this size.
Go ahead,
Kenny from the phone.
Um, is it true that
they regurgitate their prey?
Um, sometimes.
I mean, if you're lucky,
you'd die right away because
of... [groans] ...suffocation.
But only
the unlucky ones survive.
Unlucky?
Yeah, because then you might
actually be conscious
when the snake comes back
to finish you off.
-[Doug] Gotcha.
-[Claire] Ooh.
Better to die.
[tense music playing]
-[Kenny] Look at that boat!
-[Doug] This is money
in the bank, baby.
[keys jingle]
-[music stops]
-[patrons chattering]
[tense music playing]
[thuds]
Hey. Let me ask you
a question.
Um, our snake guy...
Mmm?
Does he seem
kind of batshit crazy?
I mean, he's best friends
with a snake.
Of course
he's a little quirky.
Yeah.
But I like him.
Really?
Yeah.
But then again,
I used up all my vacation days
to come make
a self-financed snake movie
with you three, so...
Yeah, your judgment
is really off.
My judgment is off.
It always has been.
Exactly.
[Doug] Anybody talk
to the captain?
It's time to shoot.
I'll, uh, reach out
again, boss.
[Doug exclaims]
[chuckles]
Hi, guys. My name is Ana.
I believe you spoke
to my father on the phone?
Bruno? That's your dad?
Yeah, he sends his apologies,
-but he's at the hospital.
-Oh.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-[Ana] Unfortunately,
you'll have to make
other accommodations,
'cause I need to take
this boat upriver
for a routine service.
But I can assure you
a full refund.
No, wait. Wait.
-Everything else is booked.
-[Griff] Yeah.
And-- And w-we're gonna
shoot a movie.
It's a reboot of Anaconda.
Technically, it's more
of a reimagining, but--
It's actually more
of a spiritual sequel.
Good for you.
There's gotta
be a way, right?
We can crew the boat.
There's nothing I can do...
We have dreamed
of making this film together
our entire lives.
Please. I am begging you.
-Please.
-Help us find another way.
Let's do this, but fast.
[Doug] Okay.
-[Claire] Yes! Let's go!
-Thank you!
[upbeat music playing]
[clanking, whirring]
-[Griff] Whoo!
-[Doug] Wow.
Oh!
[Griff] Wow!
Yes!
This is so beautiful.
This is amazing. It's amazing.
Looks exactly...
[Doug laughs]
Ooh, look!
Kenny?
[Kenny] Yeah, bud?
How did you find this boat?
Cocktail, anyone?
[Griff] Nice!
[Doug] Ah!
[Kenny] It's a computer.
Yes!
[in Portuguese]
[drawer opens]
[guitar playing]
-[all laughing]
-[glass clinking]
-[Griff] Uh-oh.
-[Claire] Oh.
[Doug] One more thing,
you guys, before we go to bed.
We got a big day tomorrow.
If you remember, we had
a tradition on all our films.
The night before
we started shooting,
we'd say a prayer
to the movie gods...
[Griff] Mm-hmm.
...asking them to basically
not screw us over,
and for the first time ever,
may they listen.
Come on, to the movie gods.
Yes.
[glasses clinking]
[Doug chuckles]
[all chattering indistinctly]
[epic music playing]
[Kenny] All right.
We're rolling.
Anaconda, scene 15,
take one. Slap it.
Bella!
-What the hell
are you still doing here?
-I've come to take you home.
It's time you stopped chasing
this mythical snake.
And what if I'm not prone
to giving up?
I didn't see you
filming there.
What are we doing? EPK?
Background, DVD, bonus stuff.
The Anaconda is a story
of an intrepid biologist
played by Claire,
who hires an unhinged
snake tracker played by Griff,
to hunt down and kill
a giant, mythical 'conda
that ate her entire family.
Come and get me,
you goddamn snake!
And on a deeper level, it's
about chasing your dreams.
And camera set,
push-ups good, and action!
What's it like
shooting with Doug again?
He and I are best friends.
We've worked together
our whole lives.
And I went out to LA,
and he was gonna come out.
We were gonna be
a partnership,
and he didn't do it.
Griff and I planned
to work together in LA, but,
uh, you know, life intervened.
But it doesn't matter,
'cause now we're together
and now we're back,
we're making this,
and it's as it should be.
I am the insects.
[Claire shrieks]
The anaconda moves
slow and steady.
Sometimes it goes fast.
Snake POV, RD. Take 1.
No. No, it's not working.
Snake POV,
the right way. Take 2.
Sometimes he goes
from above in the trees,
sometimes from below
in the water.
The toothpick, it unlocked
a couple of aspects
of this character for me.
There's something there.
Ah!
Why would I be nervous about
doing a love story with Griff?
You guys used to date.
That was a long time ago.
A little bit of chaos
is part of the ingredients.
[grunts, groans]
[shrieks]
[Doug] Maybe look
at each other.
This might be the last time
you look at each other.
You'd think you'd be
a little nicer to the guy
who's out here
to save your life.
You're an asshole.
[laughs]
Yeah.
And a PhD.
And cut.
-Great stuff, guys. We got it.
-Whoo-hoo!
Should we go one more time?
You wanna try it again?
No. I'm good if you're good.
Let's go one more time.
[animals chirping in distance]
[gentle music playing]
The chemistry
between you two is...
Yeah?
Like we were
right back in high school.
[chuckles]
When you looked up at her...
Well, that's
'cause of your note.
About taking the beat
right before you did it?
Yeah, yeah. It made the scene.
I tell you... [sighs]
[stutters] I never felt
like this on S.W.A.T.
I mean, granted I was only
in a couple of episodes,
but it was
never collaborative.
It was never fun.
Not... [scoffs]
Not like this. This, uh...
This is--
Like we were
back on Quatch?
Yeah. [chuckles]
Yeah.
[Doug] Do you guys
have chupacabra?
[Claire] Ooh.
That looks so good.
Mm-mmm.
Hey, so, one script thing.
I was thinking,
at the midway point,
instead of, uh,
talking the bad guy out of it,
what if...
Claire's character...
headbutts him?
Sorry. Headbutts him?
Headbutts him.
Or... Or...
we both do.
Double headbutt.
[Claire scoffs]
-Come on.
It's kinda revolutionary.
-[Kenny] Double headbutt.
That is super revolutionary.
Why is that
super revolutionary?
Well, it's... [stutters]
...never been done.
Jesus Christ.
This is a beautiful scene
with real stakes, Doug.
Feel free to weigh in here.
Nah, I hear you. I do.
And, as always, I trust
your instincts on this.
But a double headbutt
is pretty revolutionary.
Right? It is--
It's very revolutionary. Yes.
-There's no denying it.
-[Kenny] None!
Oh, come on, Claire.
Is the problem that you don't
know how to headbutt?
Why would I not know
how to headbutt?
[Griff] We're not born
with these skills.
We learn them along the way.
Let me show you.
Tight core, breathe in,
hold that breath.
[Claire] Yeah?
Hi-yah!
[Griff] And you
can vocalize.
Wow.
Another kind of headbutt
is more unleashed,
just full-on...
[exclaims] Whoo!
He got the arms in there.
That's good.
Send that shit into the goal.
Or you put some Brazilian
sauce on that. You know?
-And you go, boom! Toma!
-[Doug] Oh!
-[Santiago] Toma!
-Toma?
Hey, I love it.
Yeah, that's right.
-Brazilian spice.
-Yeah!
If I was gonna headbutt,
I would go for the bridge
of the nose.
-Yes.
-Just crack it. Hi-yah!
-Jesus!
-Yes! That's it.
-Jeez. Yeah, that's great.
-And you go, "Toma! Toma!"
-[exclaims]
-[exclaiming]
I think it's a different...
Toma!
-[Santiago] Toma!
-[Kenny] Yeah, toma!
[all chattering excitedly]
[Griff] Goddamn!
[creaking]
[ominous music playing]
[Doug snoring]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[shrieks]
I'm sorry, but how
could this happen, huh?
Kenny, I thought you said
this guy was a pro.
That's what he said,
but he hasn't provided us
with a certificate.
You fixed the crate, right?
It's taken care of?
My thing. My job.
Under control. All good.
My Heitor,
he's a beautiful, intelligent,
smart, sexy creature.
He does exactly
what I command.
And I would never
let anything happen
to you or the crazy one,
or her, or her,
or this "actor" here.
-What the...
-So have a good night.
May the sounds of the forest
be the music of your dreams.
Jesus...
Man, he's a poet.
Okay. Actors, on your marks.
Santiago, is Heitor ready?
Yes, Heitor is always ready.
Heitor is ready, and action!
[whimpers] Cut, please.
Um, cut? All right, cut. Yeah.
Yeah, I just-- Sorry.
I need a little...
Kenny, do you mind if I...
Santiago, take five.
Heitor, five.
Hey. Wow, that thing,
it's really...
Hey.
It's huge when you see it
up close and personal
like that.
Majestic creature.
But I just was wondering...
I throw myself in front of
the snake to kind of
protect Claire's character,
right?
Correct.
Is there any value
in not doing that?
What? No.
No, no,
he sacrifices himself for her.
Yeah. Of course.
It caps his arc.
It's so important.
Right. Right.
And also, dude,
it's totally safe.
Yeah.
Santiago has Heitor
under control.
Okay.
You've got nothing
to worry about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're good. You're good.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
All right, let's do this.
All right,
take it from the top.
Back to one.
Santiago, Heitor? Action!
Go!
I'm not leaving!
Not without you, Derek.
This thing's got me.
The world's depending on you.
I'm depending on you.
Goddamn it!
I love you, Derek van Hoyle!
It's just-- I can't-- [groans]
-Put your face
right up next to the snake.
-I don't like this.
-I don't want
to do it anymore.
-Get a tiny bit closer.
Get closer. He's friendly.
-I think you got it, dude!
-No, I don't quite have it!
-Doug, you got the shot!
-Hold it!
Just a couple more beats.
This is gold.
Just give me one more second.
One inch closer to your face.
-Get it right up in there!
-[hissing]
-You're a hero! No!
-[exclaims]
-[splashing]
-No!
[no audio]
[slowed down] Oh, shit.
I know you think
this is strange.
A grown man getting emotional
over some dead snake.
[whimpers] Jesus.
But I loved him,
and he loved me back,
whatever way he could.
[groaning]
God. No!
[Kenny crying]
Why is Kenny crying?
[kissing]
[Griff] Ugh!
Hey. I don't want you here.
Not for this!
He tried to murder me.
Griff?
What?
-Let the man grieve.
-You murdered my friend.
Just get out of my face.
-What...
Where am I supposed to go?
-Griff! Go! Just move!
Fine!
♪ Go in peace, my friend ♪
♪ May the divine snakes
Welcome you ♪
♪ My dear friend ♪
-[Claire] ♪ Snakedy snake ♪
-♪ Snakedy snake, yeah ♪
[all] ♪ Snakedy snake ♪
♪ May the divine snakes ♪
♪ Welcome you
Welcome you... ♪
[in Portuguese]
-[loud thump]
-[water sloshing]
[faint singing]
[radio static crackles]
[breathing heavily]
[singing continues]
[screams]
Timo?
Timo!
[Boyz II Men singing
"End of the Road"]
-No. Not you. No. Just--
-I know, I'm sorry...
I don't mean--
I'm not trying
to disturb you.
Just leave me alone.
I'm sorry for your loss.
[music stops]
I know you don't believe me,
but it's true. I really am.
A friend of mine
died once too, and it hurts.
Was it a snake?
No.
It was just a... human person.
Oh.
Yeah, still sad, right?
Totally. Anyway, I just
wanted to say I'm sorry.
Beer?
Well, I have my pills here,
but, yeah. Let's mix it up.
A few commercials, TV.
Did a few episodes of S.W.A.T.
Oh! S.W.A.T.?
Yeah.
I like that one.
I swear, I even had
the last line-- Thanks.
The last-- Thanks.
Last line of season three.
So, what happened?
Well, the producers decided
that they didn't really
need that character,
so they got rid of me.
I mean, it's only been going
about eight or nine
more seasons.
They don't deserve you.
[scoffs]
Yeah, you're a star.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You've been in movies?
I'm in an industrial...
You know what movie I like?
What?
The Legend of Bagger Vance.
[exhales]
You should
do a movie like that.
Man, I wish.
Yeah.
I like you.
I like you too.
You know what?
What?
I'll get a new snake
for your movie now.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
Yeah.
You come with me, of course.
What?
[Griff] Should we be in here?
Maybe we should head back.
-[water sloshes]
-What was that?
What was that?
[shushing]
Listen.
There are snakes around here.
I can feel it.
[Griff]
What does it feel like?
I don't know.
It's just very snaky.
What's-- It's snaky?
Ah.
They hear
from vibrations on the ground.
Every step we take,
drawing them closer.
And when
the jungle goes quiet...
that's when
you know they're close.
[Santiago] Yeah.
Hey, maybe we should
go back to the boat, huh?
Think it'd be a good idea
to go back to the boat.
Let's go back to the boat.
[whispering] Santiago.
Santiago.
[shouting] Santiago!
[animal squawking]
Nope.
[gasping, panting]
Where are you?
[screaming]
Hey. Have you seen Santiago?
I don't think he's come back.
Back? From what?
We went out to go
get a new snake. We--
You went to find a snake
in the middle of the night?
Yeah,
we need one for the movie.
It was dark. We got separated.
It was crazy out there.
Griff, Griff,
Griff, Griff.
What?
You went out in the middle
of the night to find
a juicy snake in the jungle?
You know what that's called?
Producing.
Really?
I guarantee he will be back
with a giant snake,
and you and I
are making movies.
You're right.
Santiago's a pro.
He'll be fine.
If he's not back soon,
we'll go look for him.
[stereo playing
Brazilian music]
[music stops]
Thank you very much, Santiago.
Guys, it's been over an hour.
I have to go find him.
Well, you're not going alone.
Yeah, we're definitely
coming with you.
It's safer that way.
[Kenny chuckles]
Have you guys
tried this thing?
It's like a warm bowl of soup
but... [laughs]
...but in chair form.
[Kenny] Yeah, man. Chairs.
They, like, hold you, man.
They literally have arms,
right?
[chuckles] Oh, wow.
Like when
your parents are gone...
we still have chairs,
you know?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Let's go find Santiago.
Let's get a snake
for our snake movie.
Yeah, Santiago! Let's go!
[animals chittering]
[tense music playing]
[whispering]
Hey, what direction
are we headed in?
Um...
Like, that way.
Wait. Kenny,
are you high right now?
Yeah, but I'm good.
I already peaked.
Jesus Christ, Kenny.
We're completely lost.
Wait. You guys, this way.
It looks like
an old camper van.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[walkie-talkie bleeps]
[in Portuguese]
[through walkie-talkie]
[Griff] What is that?
[Kenny chuckles] Oh, maybe
Santiago's sleeping in there.
[Doug] Hola.
[animals chittering]
[Doug] Whoa.
Looks totally abandoned.
Anybody home?
[Claire sighs]
Maybe some food and water.
Yeah. We could stay here.
At least tonight.
Oh, man, there's gotta be
snacks in here.
[rustling nearby]
[shushes]
[rustling]
[tense music playing]
[Ana breathes shakily]
[all breathing shakily]
[all scream]
Oh, my God.
-[Kenny] Oh, God.
-[Doug] Santiago!
[Claire] Oh, God.
[Doug gasps]
[Kenny] Dang!
That's where that guy went!
Oh, my God.
What is out there?
[tense music playing]
[growling]
[Claire breathes shakily]
-[Ana] We gotta go now!
-Okay. Go, go, go.
-Let's get out of here.
-[Ana] Let's go, let's go.
-We can't let it
crush the van.
-Crush the van?
-It's not working.
-[engine sputtering]
What?
-It's not--
-Damn it!
-It's a camper van, probably!
-Oh, God!
It's got a split-- [stutters]
a split-charge battery.
The relay probably popped off.
It's underneath the hood.
Kenny, can you fix it?
Usually I could fix it, yes,
but I'm having--
I'm still having
some visual problems
because of the... [chuckles]
You did it to me again.
You did it
on the wedding video
and now you're wasted
off your ass again.
I'm really sorry, boss.
[groans] Buffalo sober.
You're Buffalo sober.
Do you have any more?
Griff, please can you fix it?
I think I'm better suited
to be our wheel man.
What are you talking about?
I've always been
a better driver than you.
No, you've been a safer driver.
I passed the driver's test
on my first try.
You took three times.
Yeah, but that was
'cause of yield.
I didn't know--
Now I know what that is.
Oh, my God. We're gonna die.
[breathes heavily]
Sorry.
I'll just fix it.
[tense music playing]
[breathes shakily]
[hood clicks open]
[hood creaking]
[creaks]
[breathes shakily]
[tense music playing]
[hood thuds, clatters]
[Claire breathes shakily]
-[engine starts]
-[growling]
[screams]
-Doug!
-Go, go, go!
Let me get up.
Hey, wait! Stop! Stop!
Griff, where are you going?
Don't leave without me!
[grunts]
Oh, shit!
[groans, cries]
You saw it, right?
What was that? They're not
supposed to get that big.
Oh, God.
It was like a dinosaur.
[screams]
[engines revving]
Hey!
Hey, maybe we can ask
these guys for help.
-Hey!
-We have to stop.
-Do not stop the car.
Ana, what is going on?
They're illegal gold miners
who patrol
the jungles
around here.
These guys are dangerous.
They'll kill anyone
who crosses
into their territory.
-Oh, shit.
They're trying to kill us.
-[Griff] Fuck!
[Doug]
Why are they shooting at us?
-[gunshot]
-[Griff exclaims]
[Claire] Griff,
can't you drive any faster?
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa.
Ana, what are you doing?
[Ana grunts]
Whoa!
[Ana grunting]
-[Doug] Kenny,
are you getting this?
-[Kenny] Yes!
Keep rolling!
[Ana groans]
Griff, faster.
[exclaims]
Only one left.
[groaning]
[tires squeal]
[door slides open]
[breathing heavily]
Where is she?
[gasps] Oh, my God.
Who? Who do...
Who do you mean?
I know there's
someone else here.
So, where is she--
[Ana exclaims]
Let's go, come on.
We gotta go. Fast.
[Claire breathing heavily]
Look, I can get you guys
out of here.
All we need to do
is keep heading north.
There's a small airport
about a day and a half
from here.
You can get us home?
[Ana] Yes.
Get us home.
I think we gotta call it.
Man, we've got
such good stuff,
and we're so close.
Really? We're going home?
[Doug] Buddy, I know.
I don't wanna go home
empty-handed either.
But we came out here
to make Anaconda,
and now we're in it.
[mumbles]
[tapping on table]
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
[sighs]
[kisses]
[exhales deeply]
[epic music playing]
Guys, emergency meeting.
Cast and crew only.
Kenny, sit down.
-[Kenny] What is that?
-New pages.
We have some time
before the next port,
and I had an idea last night
that I think is just
too damn good not to shoot.
Doug, everybody's
pretty burnt, man.
Just hear me out.
I'm begging you please, Kenny.
All right. Sorry, boss.
[Doug] Thank you.
What if you two, on your way
to find the anaconda,
ran into a total badass
on an incredible quest?
Oh. That's interesting.
Let me guess,
to expose illegal gold miners?
Bingo.
Raises the stakes.
[Doug] Exactly.
And while they're hunting down
this mythical snake,
they actually end up
fighting the real villain.
An even bigger snake.
Man.
Oh, yeah. Yes.
I like this.
This is good.
And if we add this element,
it does make the movie
much bigger.
Like, now,
it's about something.
Themes.
Themes. [chuckles]
Uh...
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay, guy--
You know what, guys?
[stammering] I didn't wanna
say anything before, but...
this thing might be
an Awards play.
[Claire gasps]
I mean, the Academy
loves social horror.
-Right?
-[Griff] Yeah.
Dude, you could be
the white Jordan Peele.
[sighs]
I was thinking the same thing.
We've been through so much,
you guys.
Let's finish this movie.
I'm in.
Let's do it.
[Griff] Yeah.
Oh... Who are you gonna get
to play this new,
awesome character?
[exclaims in Portuguese]
[Kenny] Ow! [groaning]
[speaking Portuguese]
And cut. Yes!
-[Ana] Was it good?
-That's what
I'm talking about.
-[Claire] Nice.
-[Kenny] Yeah.
-You sure you've never
acted before?
-I swear.
Some of the best acting
I've ever seen.
You're a natural.
You're incredible.
[Claire] Thank you.
Take five. Next up, we got 72.
Guys, you see
what I'm saying?
Yeah.
-She's incredible, right?
-Yeah.
Hey... [stammers]
...a question, though.
If-- If she saves us,
it doesn't really give
my character anything to do.
Yeah.
This was supposed to be
the moment
where my character
starts falling for Derek,
so he needs to do
something heroic, you know?
Unselfish.
I don't know, you guys,
this just feels like
her moment,
she actually did it
in real life.
But good news, I'm gonna shoot
all the rest on her
so you guys have the day off.
See you later.
Take the day off.
Huh.
[gentle music playing]
[Claire]
This is our movie, Griff,
and he's just cutting us out.
[Griff] Yep. Welcome
to show business, baby.
You're not in it unless
you're getting screwed over
by your friends.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
You ever wake up and wonder
what the hell have I done
with my life?
[chuckling] Oh, yeah.
Like, every day.
Mmm.
Hey, at least you had the guts
to go after what you wanted.
No.
You think I wanted
to go to law school?
What have I got to show
for it though, huh?
You know what I have?
I have a terrible apartment
and a 74-year-old roommate.
[sighs] Sometimes
I go to Trader Joe's
just to feel air conditioning.
You at least have a career.
I mean, what do I have
to show for it?
I've got no family. No career.
Never done anything
that matters.
No nothing.
[sighs]
It's never too late.
[knocking on door]
[Doug]
Griff, I know you're in there.
Let's make a movie.
[Griff groans]
Ugh.
Hola, amigo.
Jesus. Come on, get dressed.
We've got a packed day.
What are you talking about?
I am dressed.
I'm dressed really...
very nicely.
All right. Can you just
take a cold shower?
We gotta film, like, now.
Here's an idea. You know what
you should call the movie?
Ana-conda. Get it?
Ana-conda, 'cause of Ana.
Can you just get in costume?
Man, you know what?
You wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for me.
Without me, you'd still
be stuck in Buffalo
shooting your bullshit
wedding videos.
[breathes heavily] Films.
Yeah, you can
tell yourself that.
My God, you know what?
I-- I-- I vouched for you too.
Even the rights holders,
they're like,
"Who is this guy?"
I said, "Trust me. He's good."
[boat approaching]
What is that?
[announcer]
Attention, all crew.
Let's get prepped
for scene 85, location Bravo.
Five minutes.
[Claire]
Are they making a movie?
[announcer]
Five minutes to arrival.
Excuse me,
are you guys shooting a movie?
We're doing a reboot
of Anaconda.
[Doug] Come again?
[crew member]
A reboot of Anaconda.
Anaconda?
-Like, Ice Cube Anaconda?
-Yeah.
Sony is rebooting it.
I know. No new ideas.
[tense music playing]
That's weird.
So, let me get this straight.
You don't have the rights
to Anaconda?
No, well, I...
Not legally.
And you've never owned
the rights to Anaconda?
I mean, who owns Anaconda?
Sony. Sony owns Anaconda.
Yeah, no, no, I know. I know.
I mean, like, you know, like,
in the larger sense.
Why would you tell us
that you had the rights
to the goddamn
Anaconda franchise
when you very much
don't have the rights
to the goddamn
Anaconda franchise?
Do we... [stammers] ...really
even need the rights?
Really? I mean, like,
who gives a shit?
-About IP?
-Yeah.
Literally everyone. [chuckles]
That's what big movies are!
That's why we're here!
You think that's
why we're here?
Yes, that's why we're here!
We almost died!
We're out in the middle of
the goddamn jungle for a lie!
I had to lie!
I had to lie to you!
You wouldn't have
come otherwise!
You wouldn't...
None of you would have--
[groans] Bullshit!
[Griff] Not bullshit.
It's why you never came out to
LA with me in the first place,
even though we had
a whole plan to work together.
Your whole life, you've just--
it's been dictated by fear.
Griff,
you're fired.
-What?
-[Doug] You're fired.
No. No, I'm not.
You can't fire me.
You know why?
Because I quit already.
Last night.
I just didn't tell
anybody yet.
So...
Too bad for you, I guess,
because I already quit.
[tense music playing]
Griff, wait!
Where are you even gonna go?
To find the Anaconda boat.
Maybe they can help me
get home.
Just think about this.
It's not safe.
That's a tiny boat.
There's a giant snake
out there.
Please don't do this.
Griff.
[boat engine starts, rumbles]
[epic music playing]
[music fades]
J.Lo?
Ice Cube?
Jon Voight?
Are you in this one?
[crew member screaming]
Help me!
Help me, man! Help me!
-Hey!
-Help me!
-It's okay. It's okay.
-Help! Help me!
-Calm down. I'll come get you.
-Oh, my...
It's okay. You're safe.
-You're safe.
-Oh, thank God.
Oh, shit! Oh, God!
-[yelps]
-[engine revving]
Oh, God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
[Claire] Doug!
Mm-hmm?
Doug, what's going on?
Why have we stopped?
Well, Ana found a great place
to shoot the next scene.
To shoot?
The next scene? What?
Look. Look, okay, I know.
Losing Griff was hard,
but between the four of us,
we can finish this film.
I'm not going home
empty-handed.
Come on, man. Without Griff...
That's not part of the plan.
Well, plans change and that's
part of filmmaking too.
No, no, Doug,
we have to go back for him.
He's not safe out there.
Yeah.
Ana. We need to turn
the boat around.
We are not turning
Yeah, we're not turning
the boat around.
Everyone off the boat now.
What's going on?
[tense music playing]
Ana, what are you doing?
This definitely
isn't the plan.
Well, plans change, Doug.
Isn't that filmmaking?
[gun cocks]
And every good film needs
a bit of a twist.
Everyone off the boat now!
[tense music playing]
Oh...
[Ana] To the dock.
[Kenny strains, grunts]
You're gonna carry these for
me back to the boat. Let's go.
And then what?
And then you're gonna
shoot us?
Now!
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me
what's inside these bags.
You wanna look at it?
Look at it.
Huh.
[Claire] Wait. Is...
Is that...
Gold?
So you're the miner?
You did all of this for money?
Very quick, Claire.
-[Doug exclaims]
-No!
I'm not gonna be part
of your sick quest for--
[Kenny] Ooh! Holy shit.
[in Portuguese]
And you, don't move!
[panting]
I'm with the government.
We track illegal gold miners.
And Ana here runs one
of the biggest rings
in Brazil.
[Ana speaking Portuguese]
Don't trust anything she says.
She's a liar.
She's a damn liar.
We're filmmakers from Buffalo.
We're working on
a spiritual sequel to Anaconda,
and I don't know
if she mentioned that,
but it's not just a reboot,
and I kicked out my friend
who had the lead,
and I gave her
a juicy-ass role,
-and this is how she treats--
-[Kenny] Really juicy!
Shut up! I don't know what
you're talking about, man.
Off-topic. Go, arrest her.
Oh, thank God.
[speaking Portuguese]
[tense music playing]
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
[gasps]
Oh, my God!
Who shot me?
That'd be me, asshole.
Griff, no. He was a good guy.
-I'm a good guy.
-He's a cop.
Look, I don't-- What?
I'm a good guy.
Drop it. On your knees now,
the four of you,
facing the water.
-[Kenny] Wait. I--
-Now.
[snake growling]
[Joao strains]
[grunts]
No, no, Ana.
Don't-- Don't do this.
[Ana] You too, Claire.
On your knees, now.
You don't have
to be this person.
I have children at home.
They're 10 and 13.
Please.
Think about what
you're doing to my kids.
Just shut your mouth.
Turn around now.
[whimpers]
[growling]
On your knees.
Now!
[both grunting]
-Toma!
-[Doug] Toma!
-Eat that shit!
-[Griff] Nice!
[groans]
For the record, that's
how you headbutt, bitch!
[Ana breathes heavily]
You won't do it.
You don't have the balls.
I know you, Claire.
You don't know me.
I don't even have kids.
[Claire yelps]
[muffled grunts]
[gasping, grunting]
Jesus Christ!
[Claire, Doug gasp]
[muffled grunting]
-[Doug pants] What a snake!
-No. No, wait. Wait.
I think the boat
is back that way!
Yeah, but so is the snake.
We can't go that way!
We gotta take this trail
and get to the high ground.
-[Doug] Wait. What's that?
-[Claire, Kenny] What?
-[Griff] What?
-[screams]
Oh, shit!
-[whimpering]
-[Claire] Oh, my God.
Did it bite you?
Yeah, you know what,
I think it bit me.
-I think it got me.
-Dougie, I know it hurts,
but we gotta get out
of here now
because the snake
is out there!
I'm sorry, I can't move.
My leg is freaking out.
[cries] What are we gonna do?
We're gonna have to piss
on you, man.
Huh?
On the bite.
It's the only way.
I thought that
was just jellyfish.
No, no, no, no.
It's all animals.
Are you sure?
Positive.
Someone's gotta piss.
I need one of your pisses.
I'd love to be able
to help out, but I'm just--
I am drained,
tapped, bone-dry.
Claire, you wanna
take care of this?
I'm wearing a onesie.
Kenny, we don't have time to
argue about this. You're up.
You know this isn't possible.
Why not?
Because he's...
Pee shy.
Pee shy?
[Kenny] I have urinary
stage fright.
I haven't been able
to pee in public in 35 years.
My life sucks!
You can do this.
You have to do this.
Whiz on me.
-[Griff] You got it, buddy.
-Okay.
-[Griff] Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah.
-You can do it.
-[Griff] You can do it.
Let it flow.
Let it flow. Yeah.
Just piss on me. Come on.
Whiz on me.
Whiz on me. Do it. Whiz on me.
You...
You don't think I want to?
I would love to piss
all over you, man.
But it's not in the cards!
Whiz on me. Now.
I can't. I'm trying.
You can do it! Whiz on me!
I'm trying my hardest!
Do it, Ken! Do it, Ken.
Do it. Do it.
That is an order!
Whiz on me now!
Okay! Okay.
[Griff] You got it, buddy.
You do it.
-There's one more problem.
-What?
I haven't told you about this.
I can only pee sitting down.
Jesus Christ!
I need a chair.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, buddy.
Come on, Kenny.
Come on, come on.
Just do it. Do it!
Come on, buddy.
[Kenny] Do it.
[suspenseful music playing]
[urine trickling]
-Yeah!
-Yes! Yes! Yes!
-[Griff] Nice!
-Yes! Yeah!
-[Doug] Yeah! Yeah!
[no audible dialogue]
[triumphant music playing]
Yeah!
[animals chittering]
[Doug breathing heavily]
[Doug whispering]
Griff, I'm sorry about
what I said before
on the boat.
The truth is,
I've been jealous of you
for a long, long time.
Jealous?
For having the balls
to do what I couldn't.
For going after
what you wanted.
Going to LA
and putting yourself on the--
[muffled grunting]
Oh, my God!
-[Kenny] Oh, shit!
-Doug!
[Kenny] Oh, my God!
[Claire gasping]
We have--
We have to go after him!
[Kenny]
We gotta get out of here.
We do not have a choice.
Come on.
[Claire panting]
Griff.
Oh, Griff.
[breathing heavily] Oh.
What did I do?
I tricked him
into coming here,
and now he's dead.
No. No.
We all chose to be here.
I wish it was me.
It should be me.
This is not your fault,
and we have to keep going.
Hey, guys, I think I found out
which way we should go.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey.
[panting]
It's a...
It's a big open field.
We gotta get across it
to get to the boat.
But we can't just run across.
It's too exposed.
The snake could come
from anywhere.
Maybe we can create
a distraction.
Yeah, yeah, maybe, but,
I mean, how do we do that?
[breathes heavily]
I mean, it's
gonna be... What?
[shushes]
[leaves rustling]
[growling]
It's here.
[gasps]
[flies buzzing]
What?
Oh, my God. Doug. Doug, no.
Oh, Dougie. Dougie.
Come on, man.
[Claire] Is he...
-Oh, Jesus Christ.
-[shushes]
[Claire crying]
Wait. Wait.
Maybe Doug is the distraction.
[sobs] How?
I know this is horrible, okay?
But if we can drag Doug out
into the field,
prop him up
and attach the boar
to his back
wouldn't we make it
really hard
for the snake to swallow him?
It'll occupy the snake
long enough
for us to get across the field
and get back to the boat.
Mmm, it's a really smart idea.
[Kenny straining]
Oh, guys, this is horrible.
If it meant saving all of us,
I'm sure Doug
would've wanted this.
I'm not sure
he would've wanted this.
Wait.
We gotta go, guys.
[Claire] What are you gonna
do? What are you doing?
[stammers, sighs]
Snakes,
they love squirrel meat.
[Claire groans]
[Kenny grunting]
[kisses]
[suspenseful music playing]
[all panting]
Wait, the snake
is right behind him.
[ethereal music playing]
[growling]
Oh.
I can't... [stammers]
[grunts]
Oh, shit!
[muffled grunting]
-He's alive! He's alive!
-He's alive!
I thought you
checked his pulse!
I did!
[Griff]
Well, you did a shitty job!
What the fuck?
[playful music playing]
-[Kenny] Doug! Watch out! Run!
-[Griff] Doug! Run!
Come on, Doug, run!
-[Kenny] Hey!
-[Griff] Run! Faster!
Hey.
Doug, run!
Doug!
-What?
-He's right behind you!
-[Griff] Run, Doug!
-[Kenny] Doug!
-[anaconda growling]
Oh, shit!
Shit, shit.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit. Shit.
Oh, shit.
Run!
-Run, Doug! Run!
-Run!
What the hell is on my back?
It's a long story! Just run!
[epic music playing]
[whimpers]
[exclaiming]
Shit!
[yelling]
[grunts, exclaims]
[exclaims]
God, help me! Ah! Jesus!
-[Doug exclaiming]
-[boar squealing]
Damn it. This thing's alive!
-This thing's alive!
-[squeals]
[exclaims]
It's trying to bite me!
[Griff] Doug! Run!
-[screaming]
-[squealing]
Holy shit!
Get back to the boat!
Get back to the boat! Go!
-Boat! Go! Go! Go!
-It was right behind me!
[Claire exclaims]
-Okay. All right. All right.
-Okay.
I think we're okay.
[Doug] Oh, God.
All right. All right. We-- Oh.
What the hell!
I thought I was dead.
[chuckles]
-How you doing, Dougie?
-[Doug panting]
I'm okay now.
Good.
I thought we lost you, man.
Can I say something?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I think I got so caught up
in wanting to play a hero,
that I lost sight
of what it is
that's really important to me.
And that's just making stuff
with you guys again.
Griff, I feel
the exact same way.
I love you guys.
I just have one question.
Whose idea was it to put
that dead squirrel
in my mouth?
It was like a group decision.
It wasn't--
Really?
Yeah, it wasn't
like one person.
Snakes love squirrel meat.
I knew it was your idea!
Guys, come on.
We gotta keep moving.
All right, well,
I made a choice
and I'm sticking with it.
Holy shit.
It's the Anaconda set.
[Claire] What happened?
It's destroyed.
[static on walkie-talkie]
Hello?
Is anyone there? Hello?
[distorted dialogue
on walkie-talkie]
Can you help us?
[crackling]
What? I...
[distorted dialogue
on walkie-talkie]
[stammering]
What? Again, sorry?
[person] Behind you!
["Back in Black" playing]
[groans]
♪ Back in black
I hit the sack ♪
♪ I've been too long
I'm glad to be back ♪
♪ Yes, I'm let loose ♪
♪ From the noose ♪
♪ That's kept me
Hanging about ♪
Holy shit. Ice Cube?
Who'd you think it was,
Jon Voight? Let's go.
♪ Yes, I'm back in black ♪
["Back in Black" fades]
Let's go, let's go,
let's go. Now.
In here.
Get in here, tube socks.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[whispers] We're good.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
The snake tore up the set.
Everybody scattered.
Lamp hit me, I'm down.
I get up, nobody there.
-What about J.Lo?
-Yeah, and Eric Stoltz?
Jenny from the block,
so she gonna be okay,
but Eric ain't from the block.
-[Kenny] Jesus.
-Damn it.
I don't know
how we're gonna do it,
but we have to kill it
before it kills us.
I'm with that, I'm with that.
Hey, how were they gonna do it
in your script?
I don't know. The writer
never finished the third act.
What?
You guys started shooting
before you knew the end?
Welcome to Hollywood,
buttercup.
That's what they do.
They just make it up
as they go along.
What was the general gist?
Do you have any idea?
Was anything--
All I know is they were
setting up pyrotechnics
all through here.
Is it still up?
It's hooked up,
but I don't know
how to work pyro.
Kenny, you know
how to ignite pyro, right?
-Not a problem, boss.
-[Ice Cube] Hey, hey.
I don't know
what y'all talking about.
I gotta go
save J.Lo and Stoltz.
Okay.
Really?
-You go.
-You're going after them?
They the homies, okay?
I can't leave 'em
out here with the ops.
I got to go and represent.
They my castmates.
Actors code. Respect.
Yeah, yeah.
Can we get a...
Do you mind?
-We're such fans
of everything you do.
-Come on, please.
Man, y'all groupied out.
Y'all groupied out.
What? Let's go.
-Yes!
-Okay. Everybody get in here.
Grin. Okay.
[shutter clicks]
Don't post that.
No, no, no.
Can we get one more
for safety?
I don't think
my face was totally in there.
No, it's fine.
It's fine, it's fine.
You're gonna need that.
Oh. You sure?
Of course.
I got another one.
All right. Keep it gangster.
Legend.
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
Oh, yeah.
It could work, right?
Hundred percent.
What are you...
What are you thinking?
Just so I'm...
Just to make sure
that it's exactly
what I'm thinking.
Which I'm sure it is,
totally. I mean...
I'm super sure.
I'm thinking
about killing that snake.
Now see, that's it,
that's what...
I was thinking that too.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Doug] Okay, here's the plan.
Griff, you get
the detonator from Kenny.
Claire,
you fire up the generators.
Kenny, you set up the cameras.
I'll get the golf cart.
We'll lure the snake
into the pyro field
and end this thing
once and for all.
You ready
for our big Hollywood ending?
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Kenny said as soon as
we get to the pyro field,
we can detonate
these one by one.
Gonna blow this bitch
sky-high.
Sky-freaking-high.
[rustling]
[shouts] Come get us, asshole!
Where is he?
["Kickstart My Heart" playing]
Oh, shit!
-Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
-Oh, shit!
-Doesn't this go faster?
-Well, take off the governor.
Underneath there.
See if you can rip it off.
Governor?
The governor!
It slows it down.
The hell you talking about,
governor?
I'm talking about
golf cart technology!
-Where'd it go?
-I don't see it.
I don't know where it is.
Keep your head on a swivel.
I don't see it anywhere.
-Whoa!
[Griff] Oh, my God!
Oh, shit.
We lost the signal.
If we don't get
this thing online in time...
Then we're all dead.
-Let's go.
Dude, you're actually
a really good driver.
Thank you.
[both scream]
[Griff] Oh, my God!
Why is there no power?
Pyro field dead ahead.
It's now or never.
[Griff] Armed and ready.
No!
All right, look.
Look for something like this.
Like this, okay.
Almost there!
It's getting closer!
It's getting closer! Oh, God!
Go faster!
Fuck. Found it!
Can I hit it now?
Hold. Hold.
Now! Hit it now!
Die, you giant snake bitch!
["Kickstart My Heart" ends]
-What the--
-What?
-It's not working!
It's not working!
-[Doug screams]
-Hit all of them.
-I am!
I'm hitting every one of 'em!
And now we die! Now we die!
Why didn't it happen?
Why isn't it...
I don't know.
Oh, wait.
[whirring]
I forgot to turn it on.
[sighs]
Yes!
Whoo-hoo!
Yes! Yes. Yes.
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
[triumphant music playing]
Did we kill it?
-No!
-Ah! Why?
Come on. The cart's stuck.
Oh, shit.
-Go!
-Go, go, go.
[all panting]
-It's a dead end.
-Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
We're all gonna die.
[roars]
[dramatic music playing]
Not on my watch, mister.
[Claire] Ah!
[all grunting]
-Oh, man.
-Gross.
[grunting]
[roaring]
[Claire] Griff, no!
-[screaming]
-[dramatic music playing]
And that's a wrap on snake.
[grunts]
["I Don't Want to Wait"
playing]
[chuckling]
♪ I don't want to wait
For our lives to be over ♪
♪ I want to know right now
What will it be ♪
♪ I don't want to wait
For our lives to be over... ♪
[applauding, cheering]
[Griff] Thank you very much.
[Doug] Thank you.
A long time ago,
a group of artists
had a vision
to one day live
their dream of making
a major motion picture.
And last year,
against all odds,
I'm proud to say
that dream was realized.
[chuckles]
As my friend Kenny
likes to say,
the snake is a metaphor
for the monsters
that come for all of us
if our dreams
remain unrealized.
And to be clear, there's also
a non-metaphor snake.
[screams]
-[crowd gasps]
-Oh, my God!
Quick shoutout to
Claire Simons and Kenny Trent!
-[Kenny]
Better luck next time!
-[Ana shouts in Portuguese]
[groans]
While we may not
have the rights...
We don't have... We definitely
don't have the rights.
This is our
completely unauthorized...
possibly illegal reboot
of the Sony classic film...
-Ladies and gentlemen,
The Anaconda!
-The Anaconda!
["Baby Got Back" playing]
-["Baby Got Back" stops]
-[doorbell rings]
Ho!
Oh!
Are you Doug McCallister?
Uh-huh.
You directed the unauthorized
version of Anaconda
even though
you didn't have the rights?
Yeah.
I saw your little movie.
[chuckles]
And I loved it. I loved it.
That's why I'm here.
I'm here because
we're doing another Anaconda,
and I want you to direct it.
Are you in?
[thuds]
["Baby Got Back" resumes]
["Baby Got Back" ends]
[birds chirping]
Guys?
Griff?
[chuckles]
[shouts] I'm alive!
[upbeat music playing]